<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 22 February 2026 and throughout this week. River levels at the Fosseway, Brokenborough, Great Somerford and Dauntsey gauges are stable but remaining high after yesterday's rain, further small rain totals are expected today. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. Please avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 23 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:35:46</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

River levels are high on the River Churn. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 23 February 2026, especially near Cerney Wick. The forecast is predominantly dry with some light rain. We expect levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 24 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T08:51:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Windrush. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 23 February 2026, including areas around Bourton on the Water, Witney, and Newbridge. The forecast is predominantly dry with some light rain. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 24 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T08:57:55</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Glyme. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 22 February 2026, especially in the Woodstock area. Predominantly light rain is expected over the next 48 hours, which may be heavy at times. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 23 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:01:51</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>River levels are high on the River Thames and its tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 22 February 2026, especially in the Kempsford area. Predominantly light rain is expected over the next 48 hours, which may be heavy at times. River levels are expected to remain high and responsive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12pm on 23 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:31:55</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Dikler. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 22 February 2026, including around Bourton on the Water. Predominantly light rain is expected over the next 48 hours, which may be heavy at times. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 23 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:00:23</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Leach. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 23 February 2026, including in the Lechlade-on-Thames area. The forecast is predominantly dry with some light rain. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 24 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T08:56:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are expected to remain high over the next few days in response to recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Sunday 22nd February 2026. Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. 
Peaks:- Mythe peaked at 4.07m on Friday morning 20th February, and Haw Bridge peaked at 5.06m on Friday morning 20th February.

Further scattered showers are forecast over the coming days. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 23 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:31:27</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Sunday 22nd February 2026. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Peaks: Bredon peaked at 2.7m Friday morning 20/02. 
Further scattered showers are forecast. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 23 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:25:06</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Thames and its tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock, especially in the Eynsham area. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 22 February 2026. Predominantly light rain is expected over the next 48 hours, which may be heavy at times. River levels are expected to remain high and responsive to further rainfall over the coming days.


We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12pm on 23 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:33:50</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Severn estuary from Gloucester to Sharpness</title>
      <description>High tides today may lead to flooding.   

Flooding is possible today, Sunday 22nd February 2026. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the Estuary from Sandhurst to Chepstow and Sharpness over the coming days. Some lengths of the flood embankment at Longney and The Noards may be overtopped. Rodley Lane, Westbury and Awre Road, Brims Pill may be flooded.  

Predicted Peaks: Sandhurst 3.5m to 3.7m during in this evenings high tides 22/02/26, and 3.4m to 3.6m for Monday morning tides 23/02/26 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid coastal roads and low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.   

This message will be updated by 13:00PM on 23 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T13:10:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high today in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Sunday 22nd February 2026. Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury: including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate &amp; Waterside gates closed at Upton upon Severn. 
Peaks: Diglis peaked at 3.73m on Thursday evening 19/02, Kempsey Yacht Club peaked at 5.82m on Thursday evening 19/02, and Saxons Lode peaked at 4.59m Thursday evening 19/02. 
Further scattered showers are forecast. We are closely monitoring the situation. Consider activating any flood protection products you may have. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 23 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:27:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Severn at Sandhurst and Maisemore</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
If you have been evacuated only return to your property once the emergency services have advised that it is safe to do so. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T13:14:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Sunday 22nd February 2026. Flooding may affect property and roads around Mill Avon Riverside including minor roads at Tirley, Chaceley, Hasfield, Hawbridge, Lower Lode, Ashleworth, Deerhurst, Wainlode and Apperley. Peaks:- Mythe and Upper Pound river gauges peaked at 4.11m on Wednesday 18/02.
Further scattered showers are forecast. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 23 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:24:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Sunday 22nd February 2026. Flooding may affect Gabb Lane at Apperley and local caravan parks. Peaks: Haw Bridge peaked at 5.1m on Wednesday 18th February. 
Further scattered showers are forecast. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 23 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-22T09:22:17</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Coln and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. A Flood Warning is in force for the River Coln from Fossebridge to Quennington.

River levels are high on the River Coln. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 23 February 2026, especially in the areas around Fossebridge, Coln St Dennis, and Bibury. The forecast is predominantly dry with some light rain. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 24 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T08:54:27</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Coln from Fossebridge to Quennington</title>
      <description>High river levels on the River Coln may cause flooding. 

River levels are high but steady on the River Coln following recent rainfall. Flooding of property and roads is expected, especially nearest the River Coln in the Fossebridge and Coln St Dennis areas. The forecast is predominantly dry with some light rain. River levels are expected to remain high and sensitive to any further rain over the coming days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Activate any flood protection products you may have. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.  Stay away from flood water - it contains hidden dangers such as open man hole covers, sewage and chemicals.  

This message will be updated by 18:00 on the 23 February 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-23T08:42:08</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
