<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>This flood alert remains in place. Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected. River levels are high but steady. Further rainfall is possible later this week and may keep river levels high and above the alert threshold. We are closely monitoring the situation and will update this message by 11:30AM on 12 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T10:42:50</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. Levels are currently high but stable. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:09:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially in the Newbridge and Standlake area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. River levels are currently high but stable. We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:12:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue, especially in the Woodstock area along the River Glyme.  The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. Levels are starting to fall slowly along the Evenlode and Glyme, but will remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:12:32</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible .

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue tonight, 11 December 2025, along the River Thames, especially in the Kempsford area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. River levels are currently high and stable. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:10:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially in the Bourton on the Water area, however is no longer expect. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. River levels are expected to remain high over the next few days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:14:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue tonight, 11 December 2025, especially in the Lechlade area.  The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. River levels are currently high but stable. We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:11:54</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries on the Upper River Thames above Cricklade</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially in the Oaksey area however it is no longer expected. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. River levels are falling slowly. We expect levels to continue to fall overnight.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:15:15</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 11 December 2025. 

River levels remain high due to recent rainfall. Flooding may continue over the next few days. 

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. 

Predicted peaks:- 

Mythe 3.8m to 4.2m on Saturday 13/11. 

Haw Bridge 4.6m to 5.0m on Saturday 13/11. 

No flooding is expected at other gauge locations currently. 

Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours which may see river levels rise further. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses . 

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T09:57:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T09:08:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 11 December 2025. Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. The River Avon is peaking at the Bredon gauge today at 2.35m. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours which may see river levels rise further. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T09:18:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>"High river levels this morning may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue along many parts of the River Thames between Lechlade and Eynsham. The forecast is for a predominantly dry night, a band of rain will pass over on Friday which may be heavy at times. River levels are expected to continue rising slowly overnight  between Farmoor and Eynsham as water moves downstream. Upstream of Shifford levels are slowly falling. River levels are expected to remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 10:00 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T17:14:58</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise at the Ross on Wye river gauge and remain high at Belmont, Old Wye Bridge and Mordiford river gauges. Flooding continues on 11 December 2025 . Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Peaks:- Hay on Wye peaked at 3.63m on 09/12 Bredwardine peaked at 5.72m at 7am on 10/12 AM, Belmont peaked at 5.35m on 10/12 PM, Old Wye Bridge peaked at 4.66m on 10/12 PM, Mordiford peaked at 4.86m on 10/12 eve. Predicted peak: Ross on Wye 4.2m to 4.3m on 11/12 PM. We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T10:06:47</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and continue to rise. Flooding continues. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. .Predicted peak: Ross on Wye 4.2m to 4.3m on 11/12 PM, Lydbrook 5.0 to 5.3m on 11/12 eve.. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T10:10:49</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 11 December 2025. 

Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. 

Predicted peaks:- 

Bewdley 3.6m to 4.0m Friday, 12/12/25. 

Worcester 4.4m to 4.7m Saturday, 13/12/25. 

Diglis 4.0m to 4.4m Saturday, 13/12/25. 

Kempsey Yacht Club 6.0m to 6.5m Saturday, 13/12/25. 

Saxons Lode 4.4m to 4.9m Saturday, 13/12/25. 

Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours which may see river levels rise further. We are closely monitoring the situation.  

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T09:57:30</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>High river levels are expected to cause flooding today. Flooding is expected on 11 December 2025. Flooding may affect property and roads around Mill Avon Riverside including minor roads at Tirley, Chaceley, Hasfield, Hawbridge, Lower Lode, Ashleworth, Deerhurst, Wainlode and Apperley. Predicted peak:- Mythe 3.8m to 4.2m Saturday, 13/12/25. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 48 hours which may see river levels rise further. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T09:56:47</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today.  Flooding is expected from the early hours of 11 December 2025.  Flooding may affect Gabb Lane at Apperley and local caravan parks. Predicted peak at Haw Bridge 4.6m to 5.0m on 13/12.  We are closely monitoring the situation.  Start acting on your flood plan if you have one.  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 12 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-11T09:51:08</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
