<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>River levels are stable or falling. Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Light rain through Sunday may cause levels to rise again. We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T12:43:57</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Churn. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially near Cerney Wick. A band of rain is expected this morning into the early afternoon (18/01/26), with isolated showers possible tomorrow. River levels are expected to remain high today.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T10:46:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Windrush. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially in the Newbridge area. A band of rain is expected this morning into the early afternoon (18/01/26), with isolated showers possible tomorrow. River levels are expected to remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T10:46:02</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>River levels remain high on parts of the River Evenlode. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially near Woodstock and Shipton under Wychwood. A band of rain is expected this morning into the early afternoon (18/01/26), with isolated showers possible tomorrow. River levels are expected to remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T10:45:59</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>River levels remain high on the River Thames. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially near Hannington Bridge. A band of rain is expected this morning into the early afternoon (18/01/26), with isolated showers possible tomorrow. River levels are falling slowly, but remain responsive to further rain fall. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T10:45:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Dikler. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially in areas of Bourton on the Water close to the River Dikler. A band of rain is expected this morning into the early afternoon (18/01/26), with isolated showers possible tomorrow. River levels are expected to remain high today.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T10:46:17</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible today, 18January 2026. Flooding may affect low-lying land and roads adjacent to the River Avon between Rugby and Bidford including Warwick, Stratford upon Avon, caravan parks and farmland. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T12:14:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high but are falling slowly today 19 January 2026. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 20 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T08:16:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>River levels are rising and flooding will continue today 19 January 2026. Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 20 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T08:16:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-19T08:12:39</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>River levels remain high on the River Thames. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, especially in areas between Buscot and Eynsham. A band of rain is expected this morning into the early afternoon (18/01/26), with isolated showers possible tomorrow. River levels are expected to remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm on 19 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-18T10:45:20</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
