<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge.
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge.
Whilst the rainfall throughout Monday has been less intense than was originally forecast, rivers levels are reacting but have taken longer than first predicted. Further flooding is possible overnight Monday and into Tuesday as river levels continue to rise slowly but steadily in response the rainfall which has already fallen and will continue to fall in places until around 10:00pm this evening.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T19:30:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>Forecast high river levels overnight may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the evening of 01 December 2025 . 
Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected this evening, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. Rain is expected until 11pm. The weather forecast is dry overnight and mostly dry on Tuesday. We expect river levels to remain high until Wednesday morning (03 Dec). 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses .  Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T20:58:12</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>Forecast high river levels overnight may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the evening of 01 December 2025 . 
Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected this evening, along the River Evenlode between Morton-in-Marsh and Shipton-under-Wychwood. Rain is expected until 10pm. The weather forecast is dry overnight and mostly dry on Tuesday. We expect river levels to remain high until Wednesday morning (03 Dec). 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses . Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T19:15:36</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>Forecast high river levels overnight may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the evening of 01 December 2025  
Flooding of low lying land and roads  is expected this evening, along the River Dikler. Rain is expected until 10pm. The weather forecast is dry overnight and mostly dry on Tuesday. We expect river levels to remain high until Wednesday morning (03 Dec). 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses . Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T19:08:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries in Gloucester</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T08:41:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Rivers in South Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T08:41:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries in Cheltenham and Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T08:41:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are currently rising as a result of heavy rainfall. Further rainfall is due to continue overnight tonight into tomorrow, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgeley. The Severn Ham, Tewkesbury may start to fill.  

Predicted peaks:-  
Mythe 3.0m to 3.5m  04/12/2025 AM 
Haw Bridge 4.1m to 4.6m 04/12/2025 PM 
Sandhurst 2.7m to 3.2m 04/12/2025 PM 
Gloucester 2.5m to 3.0m 05/12/2025 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.   
This message will be updated by 09:00am on 2 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T15:37:18</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>River levels are rising as a result of heavy rainfall. Heavy rain is due to continue overnight and into tomorrow, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days 

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge. Water may be over the road at Upleadon Couty.  

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses.  

This message will be updated by 10:00am On 2 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T16:24:54</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are currently rising as a result of heavy rainfall. Further rainfall is due to continue overnight tonight into tomorrow, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury may be impacted.  

Predicted peaks:-  
Evesham  1.8m to 2.3m 02/12/2025 PM 
Bredon 1.8m to 2.3m  03/12/2025 AM 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.   
This message will be updated by 09:00am on 2 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T15:37:15</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>Forecast rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 01 December 2025 . 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Predicted peaks:- Hay on Wye 3.5m to 4.0m on 02/12 AM, Bredwardine 5.3m to 5.8m on 02/12 PM, Belmont 5.5m to 6.0m on 02/12 PM, Old Wye Bridge 4.7m to 5.2m on 02/12 PM, Mordiford 4.7m to 5.2m on 02/12 Evening, Ross on Wye 3.5m to 4.0m on 03/12 AM.  Current peaks provided are low confidence and based on forecast rain only. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T09:50:51</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Rivers in the Forest of Dean</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T08:41:16</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>Forecast rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the early hours of 02 December 2025 . 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Predicted peaks:- Ross on Wye 3.5m to 4.0m 02/12 PM, Lydbrook 5.0m to 5.5m 02/12 Evening. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T14:29:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are currently rising as a result of heavy rainfall. Further rainfall is due to continue overnight tonight into tomorrow, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days. 
Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains may affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. 

Predicted peaks:- 
Bewdley 3.4m to 4.0m 04/12/2025 AM 
Worcester 3.5m to 4.0m 04/12/2025 AM 
Diglis 3.5m to 4.0m 04/12/2025 AM 
Kempsey Yacht Club 5.5m to 6.0m 04/12/2025 PM 
Saxons Lode 4.0m to 4.5m 04/12/2025 PM 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.  Consider the installation of property flood resilience measures 

This message will be updated by 09:00am on 2 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-01T15:37:23</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
