<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 05 February 2026 and throughout the week. River levels are currently decreasing at the Great Somerford gauge but are expected to rise in response to overnight rainfall. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Further rain is expected today and throughout the weekend. We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. Please avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 06 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T11:54:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

River levels are high on parts of the River Churn. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 05 Feb 2026, especially near Cerney Wick. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday. We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T07:12:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on parts of the River Windrush. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 05 Feb 2026, including areas around Bourton on the Water, Witney, and Newbridge. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T07:20:57</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Evenlode and along the River Glyme. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 05 Feb 2026, including areas around Shipton-under-Wychwood and Woodstock. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday.  We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T07:27:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Thames and its tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 05 Feb 2026, including in the Kempsford area. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday. River levels are high, but steady and we expect river levels to remain high for the next few days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T07:57:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Dikler. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 05 Feb 2026, including around Bourton on the Water. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday.  We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T07:25:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on parts of the River Leach. Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, 05 Feb 2026, especially in the Lechlade-on-Thames area. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday.  River levels are falling and we expect this to continue.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T07:18:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Thursday 5 February, and in the coming days.  Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Flooding will affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury may fill. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 6 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T09:23:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Thursday 5 February, and in the coming days.  Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 6 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T09:22:28</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Thursday 5 February, and in the coming days.  Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Peaks:- Evesham peaked 1.44m Wednesday PM, Bredon peaked 2.18m Thursday AM.  We are closely monitoring the situation.  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 6 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T09:26:36</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on parts of the River Thames and its tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 05 Feb 2026. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday.  River levels are expected to rise today and remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T08:02:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Severn estuary from Gloucester to Sharpness</title>
      <description>A series of high tides over the next few days may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible until Friday 06/02. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the Estuary from Sandhurst to Chepstow and Sharpness. Some lengths of the flood embankment at Longney and The Noards may be overtopped. Rodley Lane, Westbury and Awre Road, Brims Pill may be flooded. Predicted peaks: Sandhurst 3.5m to 3.7m Thursday 05/02 at 12:00 PM, and 3.5m to 3.7m Friday 06/02 at 00:15 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 1:00PM on 6 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T11:58:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the early hours of 06 February 2026 . 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Predicted peaks:- , Mordiford 4m to 4.3m on 06/02 PM, Ross on Wye 3.7m to 4.0m on 07/02 AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 06 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T20:16:08</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers in the Forest of Dean</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 05 February 2026 . 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from Gloucester to Chepstow. Other locations that may be affected include Westbury and Lydney. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 06 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T15:43:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the early hours of 06 February 2026 . 
Flooding mat effect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Predicted peaks:-Ross on Wye 3.7m to 4.0m on 07/02 AM, Lydbrook 4.3m to 4.6m on 07/02 PM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 06 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T20:27:28</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Thursday 5 February, and in the coming days.  Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury: including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. Peaks:- Bewdley peaked 2.51m Thursday AM, Worcester peaked 3.15m Thursday AM, Diglis peaked 2.90m Thursday AM, Kempsey Yacht Club peaking at 5.05m Thursday AM and Saxons Lode peaked 3.93m Thursday AM.  We are closely monitoring the situation.  Consider activating any flood protection products you may have. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 6 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T09:26:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Wye Estuary in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>High tides may lead to flooding on Thursday evening and Friday morning. Whilst the period of high tides is coming to an end, river levels will remain over the coming days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the Wye Estuary from Redbrook to Chepstow. Predicted peaks:- Avonmouth Portbury 6.9m to 7.2m Thursday 05/02 at 9:45 PM and 6.9m to 7.1m Friday 06/02 at 10:00 AM. Newport 6.5m to 6.7m Thursday 05/02 at 9:30 PM and 6.5m to 6.7m Friday 06/02 at 09:45 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 1:00PM on 6 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T16:45:02</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Coln and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on parts of the River Coln. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 05 Feb 2026, especially in the Fossebridge area. Rain and heavy showers are forecast for today and Friday.  We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 06 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-05T07:15:41</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
