<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>This flood alert remains in place. Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected. Further rainfall is forecast today 05/12/25 and over the weekend. River levels are forecast to rise further in the coming days and the flood risk remains.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T11:38:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

Flooding is possible from the morning of the 05 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. The weather forecast is for further rain which could be heavy at times over the next 3 days. We expect river levels to stay high.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 19:00 05 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T09:36:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

Flooding is possible from the evening of the 05 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, 05 Dec 2025, along the River Thames, especially in the Kempsford area. This is as a result of rivers responding to recent rainfall. The weather forecast is for further rain which could be heavy at times over the next 3 days. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are closely monitoring the situation.

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 1900 05 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T09:38:22</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high due to recent rainfall, flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgeley. The Severn Ham, Tewkesbury may start to fill.  

River levels are currently peaking and will remain high over the next few days. Additional rainfall is forecast Friday 05/12/2025 onwards, which may cause river levels to rise further.  

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.  

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 6 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T08:27:48</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tidal River Avon at Bristol, Pill and Shirehampton</title>
      <description>High tides over the next two days may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from 07:00PM to 08:00PM on 05/12/2025 and 07:00AM and 08:00AM on 06/12/2025 
Areas most at risk include the tidal River Avon from Sea Mills to Conham in Bristol and between the Avonmouth Bridge and Shirehampton Park including Pill and Shirehampton. The first forecast high water at Avonmouth is 7.48mAODN at 07:15pm this evening 05/12/2025, with South Westerly Force 5 winds. The second forecast high water is at 7:30am on Saturday 06/12/2025 with a level of 7.61mAODN and Force 7 South Westerly winds. mAODN is height above average sea level. Flooding to roads and farmland is possible but properties are not currently expected to flood. 
We are closely monitoring the situation and our incident response staff will be on site closing flood gates 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water and don't put yourself or others at risk 
This message will be updated by 12:30PM on 06 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T12:11:07</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Severn estuary from Gloucester to Sharpness</title>
      <description>Higher than normal tides on Friday evening and Saturday morning may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from 9:15pm on Friday evening and 9:30am on Saturday morning. 

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the Estuary from Sandhurst to Chepstow and Sharpness over the coming days. Some lengths of the flood embankment at Longney and The Noards may be overtopped. Rodley Lane, Westbury and Awre Road, Brims Pill may be flooded.  

Predicted peaks: - 
Friday evening 05/12; Gloucester 3.45m to 3.65m at 9:15PM, Sandhurst 3.5m to 3.7m at 9:30PM.  
Saturday morning 06/12; Gloucester 3.5m to 3.7m at 9:30AM, Sandhurst 3.6m to 3.8m at 9:45AM.  

We are closely monitoring the situation. Please continue to monitor local water levels and weather conditions.  

This message will be updated by 2:00PM on 06 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T13:39:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>The flood forecast has changed significantly. As a result, there is no longer a risk of flooding in the area. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected. The flood forecast has changed significantly. As a result, there is no longer a risk of flooding in the area. 
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-04T16:24:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Wye Estuary in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>High tides today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from 7:15pm on Friday evening and 7:30am on Saturday morning. 
Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers or on the coast.

Predicted peaks: - 
  
Friday evening 05/12; Avonmouth 7.3m to 7.6m at 7:15PM, Newport 7m to 7.3m at 7:15PM.  
  
Saturday morning 06/12; Avonmouth 7.4m to 7.7m at 7:30AM, Newport 7.1m to 7.4m at 7:30AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation  
Monitor local water levels and weather conditions  
This message will be updated by 2:00PM on 06 December 2025 or as the situation changes.

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-05T14:22:11</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
