<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>This flood alert remains in place. Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected. River levels are high and rising. Further rainfall is expected tomorrow, the 18th December and will keep river levels high. We are closely monitoring the situation and will update this message by 11:30AM on 18 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T18:46:49</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 18 December 2025, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. Levels along the River Churn are currently high but stable. Heavy rain is forecast today, 18 December 2025, with a chance of further heavy showers tomorrow and through the weekend. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 07:00PM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:46:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue tonight, 17 December 2025, especially along the River Windrush in the Bourton on the Water, Newbridge and Standlake areas. Heavy overnight rain is forecast tonight, 17 December 2025, with further heavy rain forecast on 18 December 2025. River levels are rising very slowly in the Witney area. Levels are expected to remain high over the coming days, and may rise further in response to forecasted rainfall over the coming 36 hours.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T20:18:32</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected tonight, 17 December 2025, especially close to the river between Moreton in Marsh and Shipton Under Wychwood on the River Evenlode. Heavy overnight rain is forecast tonight, 17 December 2025, with further heavy rain forecast on 18 December 2025. Levels are expected to remain high over the coming days, and may rise further in response to forecasted rainfall over the coming 36 hours. Levels on the River Glyme are currently stable and below the flood risk threshold. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T20:32:13</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding remains possible.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue tonight, 17 December 2025, along the River Thames, especially in the Kempsford area. Heavy overnight rain is forecast tonight, 17 December 2025, with further heavy rain forecast on 18 December 2025. River levels are currently high but stable. Levels are expected to remain high over the coming days, and may rise further in response to forecasted rainfall over the coming 36 hours.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T19:58:57</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible tonight, 17 December 2025, especially in the Bourton on the Water area. Heavy overnight rain is forecast tonight, 17 December 2025, with further heavy rain forecast on 18 December 2025. Levels are expected to remain high over the coming days, and may rise further in response to forecasted rainfall over the coming 36 hours.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T20:57:12</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue tonight, 17 December 2025, especially in the Lechlade area. Heavy overnight rain is forecast tonight, 17 December 2025, with further heavy rain forecast on 18 December 2025. River levels are currently high but stable. River levels may rise further due to recent rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T20:06:47</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries on the Upper River Thames above Cricklade</title>
      <description>High river levels this evening may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue tonight, 17 December 2025, especially close to the Swill Brook in the Oaksey area. Heavy overnight rain is forecast tonight, 17 December 2025, with further heavy rain forecast on 18 December 2025. Levels are expected to remain high over the coming days, and may rise further in response to forecasted rainfall over the coming 36 hours.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T21:27:23</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>Although some river levels are still rising, some river levels are forecast to fall during today, though may rise again overnight in response to further forecast rainfall.  Flooding is possible on 18 December 2025.  Flooding may affect low-lying land and roads adjacent to the River Avon between Rugby and Bidford including Warwick, Stratford upon Avon, caravan parks and farmland. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T11:18:30</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries in Gloucester</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding.  Flooding is possible from 18 December 2025 .  Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to Horsbere Brook, Wotton Brook, River Twyver, River Sud, Whaddon Brook, Daniels Brook &amp; Dimore Brook. Locations that may be affected include Kemerton, Tewkesbury, Stoke Orchard, Uckington, Churchdown, Upton St Leonards, Cheltenham, Horsebere and Brookthorpe. The Horsbere flood storage area may become operational.  We are closely monitoring the situation.  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 19 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T06:35:54</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Little Avon catchment and the Vale of Berkeley</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 17 December 2025. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Little Avon, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around Areas most at risk include the Little Avon River and other rivers and streams in the Vale of Berkeley. Further rainfall is forecast on Wednesday and Thursday and this Alert is likely to remain in force. We are monitoring rainfall and river levels and will issue updates as necessary. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 10:30AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T10:21:27</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers in South Worcestershire</title>
      <description>Forecast rising river levels this evening may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 18 December 2025 . 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from North Littleton to Winchcombe. Other locations that may be affected are Badsey, Childswickham, Broadway, Sedgeberrow, Toddington and the Road at Hinton on the Green bridge. This alert has been issued based on uncertain forecast heavy rainfall that may have significant impact within the community. As the rain has not yet fallen and been observed we are unable to provide any real time peak information. As the situation evolves we will be able to provide more details. 
We are closely monitoring the situation and monitoring River levels. 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T15:43:01</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries in Cheltenham and Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from 18 December 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to Wymans Brook, Carrant Brook, Hatherley Brook, Swilgate and the River Chelt. Locations that may be affected include Mitton, Ashchurch, Walton Cardiff and locations along the River Chelt from Charlton Kings to Uckington and Boddington.  We are monitoring rainfall and river levels   Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 19 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T06:40:05</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from 18 December 2025 over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgeley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. Predicted peaks:- Mythe 3.6m to 4.1m on 20/12/25 PM Haw Bridge 4.6m to 5.1m on 20/12/25 PM. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours, and this may cause river levels to rise again. We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 19 December 2025 or as the situation changes
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:47:33</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from the 18 December 2025 . Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court. We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 19 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T06:27:13</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from 18 December 2025 for the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubilee Bridge to Fladbury may be impacted. Peaks:- Evesham 2.4m - 2.8m Friday AM,  Bredon 2.3m to 2.5m overnight Thursday 18/12 PM.  Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 19 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:31:05</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Bristol Frome catchment</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 17 December 2025. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Frome, Bristol Floating Harbour, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around Areas most at risk include St John's Way in Chipping Sodbury and Damson Bridge. Further rainfall is forecast on Wednesday and Thursday and this Alert is likely to remain in force. We are monitoring rainfall and river levels and will issue updates as necessary. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. The road may be flooded at Damson Bridge. This message will be updated by 10:30AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T10:24:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected tonight, 17 December 2025, particularly along the River Thames between Lechlade and Shifford. Heavy overnight rain is forecast tonight, 17 December 2025, with further heavy rain forecast on 18 December 2025. River levels are rising slowly in response to recent rainfall along much of the Upper Thames. It is expected that river levels will rise further in response to forecasted rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T21:04:43</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from the early hours of 18 December 2025 . 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Predicted peaks:-  Bredwardine 4.9m to 5.4m on 19/12 AM, , Old Wye Bridge 4.3m to 4.8m on 19/12 AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T15:45:47</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers in the Forest of Dean</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from the afternoon of 18 December 2025 . Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from Gloucester to Chepstow. Other locations that may be affected include Westbury and Lydney. We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 19 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T06:31:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 17 December 2025.  

Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. 

Peaks:- 

Bewdley has peaked today at 2.78m 

Worcester has peaked today at 3.37m 

Diglis has peaked today at 3.09m 

Kempsey Yacht Club has peaked today at 5.20m 

Saxons Lode is peaking today at 3.98m. 

Further rainfall is forecast on Wednesday evening into Thursday, and this may cause river levels to rise again. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 18 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-17T09:33:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today.  Flooding is expected from 18 December 2025 over the next few days. Flooding may affect property and roads in and around Severn Ham and access to Abbey Mill may be compromised. Predicted peak:- Mythe 3.6m to 4.1m on 20/12/25 PM.  We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Monitor local water levels and weather conditions.  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 19 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-18T08:36:36</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
