<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 1 March 2026. River levels at the Fosseway, Brokenborough, Great Somerford and Dauntsey gauges are falling slowly. Flooding is possible at locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. We are closely monitoring the situation. Please avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 11:00 AM on 2 March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T10:55:02</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Churn. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026, especially near Cerney Wick. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2025, before a dry day tomorrow. Levels remain high but stable. We expect levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:13:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Windrush. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026, including areas around Bourton on the Water, Witney, and Newbridge. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2025, before a dry day tomorrow. River levels are high but stable. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:22:17</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Glyme. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026, especially in the Woodstock area. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2025, before a dry day tomorrow. Levels on the River Evenlode have fallen below the flood risk threshold. Levels on the River Glyme are high but stable. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:26:44</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

River levels are high on the River Thames and its tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026, especially in the Hannington Wick area. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2026, before a dry day tomorrow. River levels are high and now stabilising. River levels are expected to remain high and responsive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:16:18</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels remain high but are now falling gradually on the River Dikler following recent rainfall. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026, including around Bourton on the Water. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2025, before a dry day tomorrow. We expect river levels to continue falling slowly over the coming days. Levels will remain sensitive to further rainfall. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:24:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high, but falling on the River Leach. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026, including in the Lechlade-on-Thames area. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2025, before a dry day tomorrow. We expect river levels to continue falling slowly but will remain sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:19:19</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>River levels remain high but are slowly decreasing at the Rugby, Warwick and Stratford river gauges. Therefore, the risk of flooding will remain throughout Sunday. Some light rainfall is forecast, but no further increases are expected, we expect levels to continue to decrease.
Flooding  may affect low-lying land and roads adjacent to the River Avon between Rugby and Bidford including Warwick, Stratford upon Avon, caravan parks and farmland.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Stay away from flood water - it contains hidden dangers such as open man hole covers, sewage and chemicals.  

This message will be updated by 11:00 Monday 2 March or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:19:29</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are expected to remain high over the next few days in response to recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Sunday 1st March 2026. Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. 
Peaks:- Mythe peaked at 4.07m on Friday morning 20th February, and Haw Bridge peaked at 5.06m on Friday morning 20th February.
Further scattered showers are forecast. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 2nd March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:03:54</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 01 March 2026 for the next 24 hours. 
Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:41:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible today, Sunday 1st March 2026. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. 
Peaks: Evesham peaked yesterday 28/02, at 2.3m. Predicted peak: Bredon 2.5m to 2.7m this morning 01/03. 
Further scattered showers are forecast. We are closely monitoring the situation.  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 2nd March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:47:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Thames and its tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2026, before a dry day tomorrow. River levels are high and rising gradually in response to recent rainfall. River levels are expected to remain high and responsive to further rainfall over the coming days.


We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:18:28</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
If you have been evacuated only return to your property once the emergency services have advised that it is safe to do so. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:12:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible today Sunday 1st March 2026. Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. 
Peaks: Bewdley peaked at 2.7m on 28/02. Predicted peaks: Worcester 3.6m to 3.7m this afternoon 01/03, Diglis 3.2m to 3.6m this afternoon 01/03, Kempsey yacht club 5.4m to  5.5m this afternoon 01/03 and Saxons Lode 4.3m to 4.5m this afternoon 01/03. 
Further scattered showers are forecast. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:40:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>Flooding is expected for: River Severn at Severn Ham, including Abbey Mill, Upper and Lower Lode and Shakespeare Court 
 Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today. 
 Flooding is expected on 01 March 2026 this afternoon and overnight. 
 Flooding may affect property and roads around Mill Avon Riverside including minor roads at Tirley, Chaceley, Hasfield, Hawbridge, Lower Lode, Ashleworth, Deerhurst, Wainlode and Apperley. Predicted peaks:- at Mythe 3.6m to 3.7m on 01/03 AM Upper Pound 3.8m to 3.9m on 01/03 AM. 
 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 March 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T09:50:28</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today. 
Flooding is expected on 01 March 2026 . 
Flooding may affect Gabb Lane at Apperley and local caravan parks. Predicted peak at Haw Bridge 4.7m to 4.8m on 01/03 PM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 02 March 2026 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:55:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Coln and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. A Flood Warning is in force for the River Coln from Fossebridge to Quennington.

River levels are high on the River Coln. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 1 March 2026, especially in the areas around Fossebridge, Coln St Dennis, and Bibury. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2025, before a dry day tomorrow. River levels are high but stable. We expect river levels to remain high and sensitive to further rainfall over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

 This message will be updated by 12.00 on 2 March 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:15:51</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Coln from Fossebridge to Quennington</title>
      <description>High river levels on the River Coln may cause flooding. 

River levels are high but stable on the River Coln. Flooding of property and roads remains possible on 1 March 2026, especially nearest the River Coln in the Fossebridge and Coln St Dennis areas. The forecast is for further light rain today, 1 March 2026, with a dry day forecast tomorrow. River levels are expected to remain high and sensitive to any further rain over the coming days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Activate any flood protection products you may have. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.  Stay away from flood water - it contains hidden dangers such as open man hole covers, sewage and chemicals.  

This message will be updated by 19:00 on the 1 March 2026, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-03-01T08:10:57</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
