<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>This flood alert remains in place. Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected. Further rainfall, heavy at times, is forecast for the next few days. River levels are steady but are forecast to start rising in response to the rain. We are closely monitoring the situation and will update this message by 11:30AM on 08 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T11:31:29</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible from the evening of the 07 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible tonight, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. The weather forecast is generally dry over night and tomorrow with some light rain.  We expect river levels to remain high.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 11:00 08 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T17:28:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>Rising river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible from the evening of 07 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially in the Newbridge area. The weather forecast is generally dry over night and tomorrow with some light rain.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 11:00 08 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T17:39:55</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible from the evening of 07 Dec 2025. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially in the Shipton under Wychwood and Woodstock areas. The weather forecast is generally dry over night and tomorrow with some light rain.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 11:00 08 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T17:43:36</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible from the evening of the 07 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible tonight, 07 Dec 2025, along the River Thames, especially in the Kempsford area. This is as a result of rivers responding to recent rainfall. The weather forecast is generally dry over night and tomorrow with some light rain. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 11:00 08 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T17:32:53</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible from the evening of 07 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially in the Lechlade area. The weather forecast is generally dry over night and tomorrow with some light rain.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 11:00 08 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T17:37:28</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high due to recent rainfall, flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. Predicted peaks during high tides: - Sunday evening 07/12; Gloucester 3.5m to 3.6m at 23:15PM, Sandhurst 3.7m to 3.9m at 23:30PM. Monday morning 08/12; Gloucester 3.5m to 3.6m at 11:30AM, Sandhurst 3.7m to 3.9m at 11:45AM. Additional rainfall is forecast over the next few days. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 2:00PM on 8 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T15:57:43</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. 

Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court.  

Further rainfall is forecast next week which may see river levels rise further. We are closely monitoring the situation.  

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  

This message will be updated by 9:00AM on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T08:54:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. 

Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted.  

River levels at Bredon are predicted to peak between 2.0m and 2.2m this morning, Sunday 07/12/25. Further rainfall is forecast next week which may see river levels rise further.  

We are closely monitoring the situation.  

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  

This message will be updated by 9:00AM on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T08:55:35</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Severn estuary from Gloucester to Sharpness</title>
      <description>High tides on Sunday evening and Monday morning may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible from 11:15pm on Sunday evening and 11:30am on Monday morning.

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the Estuary from Sandhurst to Chepstow and Sharpness over the coming days. Some lengths of the flood embankment at Longney and The Noards may be overtopped. Rodley Lane, Westbury and Awre Road, Brims Pill may be flooded. 

Predicted peaks: - 
Sunday evening 07/12; Gloucester 3.5m to 3.6m at 23:15PM, Sandhurst 3.7m to 3.9m at 23:30PM. 
Monday morning 08/12; Gloucester 3.5m to 3.6m at 11:30AM, Sandhurst 3.7m to 3.9m at 11:45AM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Please continue to monitor local water levels and weather conditions. 

This message will be updated by 2:00PM on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T15:55:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>High river levels today have led to flooding.  Flooding is possible on 07 December 2025 .  Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Peaks:- Hay on Wye 2.36m at 20:30 06/12, Bredwardine 4.39m at 00:00 07/12, Belmont 4.50m at 05:00 07/12, Old Wye Bridge 3.90 at 04:45 07/12, Mordiford 4.3m to 4.4m on 07/12 AM, Ross on Wye 3.6m to 3.9m on 07/12 PM. .  We are closely monitoring the situation .  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T08:55:19</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding.  Flooding is possible on 07 December 2025 .  Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Predicted peaks:- Ross on Wye 3.6m to 3.9m 07/12 PM, Lydbrook 4.7m to 4.9m 07/12 PM.  We are closely monitoring the situation .  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T08:38:51</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. 

Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. 

Predicted peaks:- 
Worcester 3.3m to 3.5m this morning, 07/12/25. 
Diglis 3.1m to 3.2m this morning, 07/12/25 
Kempsey Yacht Club 5.2m to 5.3m this morning, 07/12/25. 
Saxons Lode 3.9m to 4.3m this morning, 07/12/25. 
Bewdley 3.2m to 3.6m on Tuesday morning, 07/12/25. 

Further rainfall is forecast next week which may see river levels rise further. We are closely monitoring the situation.  

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  

This message will be updated by 9:00AM on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T08:56:16</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Sandhurst and Maisemore</title>
      <description>High river levels are expected to cause flooding Sunday evening. Flooding is expected on 07/12/2025. During high tides, flooding may affect Coal Wharf and Riverside, Maisemore and Sandhurst Lane. A417 Over to Maisemore (fluvial and tidal). Properties in Base Lane Sandhurst, Sandhurst Lane and Riverside, Maisemore. Predicted peaks:- Sunday evening 07/12; Gloucester 3.5m to 3.6m at 11:15PM, Sandhurst 3.7m to 3.9m at 11:30PM. Monday morning 08/12; Gloucester 3.5m to 3.6m at 11:30AM, Sandhurst 3.7m to 3.9m at 11:45AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 2:00pm on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T12:48:18</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>High river levels are expected to cause flooding overnight. 
Flooding is expected on 07 December 2025 . 
Flooding may affect property and roads around Mill Avon Riverside including minor roads at Tirley, Chaceley, Hasfield, Hawbridge, Lower Lode, Ashleworth, Deerhurst, Wainlode and Apperley. Predicted peaks:- at Mythe 3.6m to 3.8m on 09/12 AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 December 2025 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-07T13:12:53</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
