<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Windrush. Therefore flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today, near Newbridge. Widespread persistant rain is expected today (Thursday 15 January) which will be heavy in places. Further rainfall possible tomorrow. We expect river levels to rise in response and to remain high over the weekend.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00 pm, midday, on the 16 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T09:53:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and flooding may continue today 15 January 2026. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. We are closely monitoring the situation. Further rainfall is forecast today 16 January 2026. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T09:34:56</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and flooding is possible today 15 January 2026 . Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Further rain is forecast today 15 January 2026. We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T09:29:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and flooding may continue today 15 January 2026. Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn.  Further rainfall is forecast today 15 January 2026. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 January 2026 or as the situation changes
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T09:32:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and flooding is expected today 15 January 2026 .  Flooding may affect Gabb Lane at Apperley and local caravan parks. Further rain is forecast today 15 January 2026. We are closely monitoring the situation .  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 January 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-15T10:10:55</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>High river levels are expected to cause flooding today. 
Flooding is expected on 14 January 2026 . 
Flooding may affect Gabb Lane at Apperley and local caravan parks. Predicted peak at Haw Bridge 4.6m to 4.7m on 14/01 AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 15 January 2026 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-01-14T07:17:34</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
