<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge.
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge.
Weather conditions have generally improved and rainfall levels are low for the next few days through until Friday when the next weather system arrives. Whilst there is an improving picture with river levels starting to reduce, levels are still high.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T19:29:39</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible tonight, 02 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected today, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. The weather forecast is mostly dry overnight and on Wednesday.  We expect river levels to remain high until Wednesday (03 Dec).

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 10:00 03 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T17:43:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible tonight, 02 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, along the River Evenlode between Moreton-in-Marsh and Shipton-under-Wychwood. The weather forecast is mostly dry overnight and on Wednesday.  We expect river levels to remain high overnight.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 10:00 03 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T17:40:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>Rising river levels overnight may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 02 December 2025 . 
Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected along reaches of the River Thames, especially in the Hannington area. This is as a result of rivers responding to recent rainfall. No rainfall is forecast overnight. We expect river levels to stabilise during the day tomorrow, 03 December 2025. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses . Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 03 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T19:26:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:47:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are currently rising due to rainfall on Monday, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgeley. The Severn Ham, Tewkesbury may start to fill.  

Predicted peaks:-  
Mythe 3.1m to 3.7m 05/12/2025 PM. 
Haw Bridge 4.0m to 4.7m 05/12/2025 PM. 

Tides are increasing from Wednesday until the weekend. River levels at Sandhurst and Gloucester will be influenced by these tides. Current predictions: 

Sandhurst 2.9m to 3.1m 03/12/2025 PM and 3.0m to 3.2m 04/12/2025 AM.  
Gloucester 2.5m to 2.8m 03/12/2025 PM and 2.8m to 3.1m 04/12/2025 AM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.   
This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 4 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:29:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T11:54:32</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-02T11:54:30</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>River levels have peaked and have started to fall at all river gauges. Flooding continues today 03 December 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. 

Observed peaks:- Hay on Wye peaked at 2.45m at 3am on 02/12/25, Bredwardine peaked at 4.41m at 8am on 02/12/25,.Belmont peaked at 4.43m at 1pm on 02/12/25, Old Wye Bridge peaked at 3.84m a 1pm on 02/12/25, Mordiford peaked at 4.23m at 5:15pm on 02/12/25, Ross on Wye peaked at 3.55m at midnight on 02/12/25  We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 04 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:27:16</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels have started to fall at all river gauges. Flooding continues today 03 December 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Observed peaks:- Ross on Wye peaked at 3.55m at midnight on 02/12/25, Lydbrook peaked at 4.27m at 4am this morning, 03/12/25.

We are closely monitoring the situation . Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 04 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:31:23</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are currently rising due to rainfall on Monday, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days. 
Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains may affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St and Waterside Gates are closed at Upton upon Severn.   

Predicted peaks:- 
Bewdley 3.0m to 3.8 m 04/12/2025 PM. 
Worcester 3.4m to 4.1m 04/12/2025 OVERNIGHT. 
Diglis 3.0m to 3.7m 05/12/2025 AM. 
Kempsey Yacht Club 5.0m to 5.7m 05/12/25 AM. 
Saxons Lode 4.1m to 4.7m 05/12/25 PM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.  Consider the installation of property flood resilience measures 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 4 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:31:21</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
