<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 07 February 2026 and throughout the weekend. River levels at the Fosseway, Brokenborough, Great Somerford and Dauntsey gauges are falling but remain high. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Further showers are forecast this weekend. We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. Please avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T10:21:43</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding.

River levels are high on parts of the River Churn. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 07 Feb 2026, especially near Cerney Wick. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:44:06</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on parts of the River Windrush. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 07 Feb 2026, including areas around Bourton on the Water, Witney, and Newbridge. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:00:29</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Evenlode and along the River Glyme. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 07 Feb 2026, including areas around Shipton-under-Wychwood and Woodstock. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. River levels are high, and rising slowly in resoponse to yesterdays rainfall. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:04:46</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>River levels are high on parts of the River Thames and its tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 07 Feb 2026, including in the Kempsford area. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. River levels are high, and rising slowly in response to yesterdays rainfall. We expect river levels to remain high for the next few days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:40:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on the River Dikler. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 07 Feb 2026, including around Bourton on the Water. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:02:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are still high on parts of the River Leach. Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, 07 Feb 2026, especially in the Lechlade-on-Thames area. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. River levels are high, and rising slowly in resoponse to yesterdays rainfall. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:48:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding.  Flooding is possible on 07 February 2026 .  Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers.  We are closely monitoring the situation .  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:37:11</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Stour in South Warwickshire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:27:39</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. Predicted peaks:- Mythe 4.2m to 4.5m on Sunday 08/02 PM, and Haw Bridge 5.1m to 5.3m on Monday 09/02 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:45:12</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:15:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Predicted peaks:- Evesham 2.7m to 2.9m on Saturday 07/02 PM, and Bredon 2.9m to 3.1m on Sunday 08/02 PM.
We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:50:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on parts of the River Thames and its tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 07 Feb 2026. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. River levels are expected to continue to rise slowly today and remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:42:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Severn estuary from Gloucester to Sharpness</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Coastal conditions are expected to improve and no flooding is expected. Although this tidal alert is no longer in force, river levels remain high due to recent rainfall. 
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:34:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 7th February 2026.
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force.
Observed peaks:- Hay-on-Wye 1.54m Friday 06/02 AM. Bredwardine 3.22m Friday 06/02 AM. Belmont 3.46m Friday 06/02 PM. Old Wye Bridge 2.96m Friday 06/02 PM. Mordiford 3.90m Friday 06/02 PM. Ross-on-Wye 3.52m Saturday 07/02 AM.
We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 8th February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:50:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers in the Forest of Dean</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 07 February 2026 . 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from Gloucester to Chepstow. Other locations that may be affected include Westbury and Lydney. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T13:42:11</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 7th February 2026. 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye.
Observed peaks:- Ross-on-Wye 3.52m Saturday 07/02 AM.
Predicted peaks:- Lydbrook peaking at 4.4m Saturday 07/02 AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 8th February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:58:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Further rainfall is forecast over the next 24 hours.
Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury: including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate closed at Upton upon Severn. Predicted peaks:- Bewdley 3.5m to 3.7m on Monday 09/02 AM, Worcester 4.7m to 4.9m on Sunday 08/02 AM, Diglis 4.5m to 4.7m on Sunday 08/02 AM, Kempsey Yacht Club 6.6m to 6.9m on Sunday 08/02 AM, and Saxons Lode 4.9m to 5.2m on Sunday 08/02 PM.
We are closely monitoring the situation. Consider activating any flood protection products you may have. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:48:21</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Flooding may affect property and roads in and around Severn Ham and access to Abbey Mill may be compromised. Predicted peaks:- Mythe 4.2m to 4.5m on Sunday 08/02 PM, and Upper Pound 4.3m to 4.7m on Sunday 08/02 PM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:11:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Flooding may affect Gabb Lane at Apperley and local caravan parks. Predicted peak at Haw Bridge 5.1m to 5.3m on Monday 09/02 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:12:58</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Chaceley and Haw Bridge</title>
      <description>High river levels are expected to cause flooding today. 
Flooding is expected on 07 February 2026 and over the coming days.   
Flooding may affect properties and roads in and around Tirley and Chaceley, including the B4213 Church Road and B4213 Haw Bridge Road at Wainlodes Junction. Predicted peak at Haw Bridge 5.1m to 5.3m on Monday 09/02 AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:13:22</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Abbots Court, Deerhurst</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Flooding may affect Abbots Court, Deerhurst. Predicted peak at Haw Bridge 5.1m to 5.3m on Monday 09/02 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:18:48</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Avon at Strensham and Bredon</title>
      <description>River levels remain high in response to the recent rainfall. Flooding is possible today, Saturday 07 February, and in the coming days. Flooding may affect properties and roads around Mill Lane, Strensham and areas around Dock Lane Bredon. Predicted peaks:- Evesham 2.7m to 2.9m on Saturday 07/02 PM, and Bredon 2.9m to 3.1m on Sunday 08/02 PM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 08 February 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T09:19:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Coln and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

River levels are high on parts of the River Coln. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, 07 Feb 2026, especially in the Fossebridge area. Further rain is forecast for today and into Sunday. We expect levels to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying footpaths and roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River Levels Online for updates on current river levels. 

This message will be updated by 12:00 on 08 Feb 2026 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2026-02-07T08:46:17</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
