<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>River levels on the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon and Dauntsey Brook remain high but are slowly dropping today. Areas most at risk include low lying land and roads around Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham and roads near Reybridge. This Flood Alert will be removed tomorrow. The weather outlook currently shows more showers for the week ahead but no significant rain storms.  We are closely monitoring the situation .  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water .  This message will be updated by 10:27AM on 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T17:29:57</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>Flooding remains possible. Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue as river levels along the River Churn remain high, particularly in Cerney Wick. The weather forecast is dry for Tuesday and Wednesday. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels. This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T13:16:02</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>Flood risk remains possible. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue as river levels along the River Windrush remain high, particularly in Bourton on the Water, Witney, Standlake and Newbridge. The weather forecast is dry Tuesday and Wednesday. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T12:00:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels have led to flooding of land close to the River Glyme. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue on the River Glyme at Woodstock. The river is now flowing within banks on the River Evenlode although water will remain in fields close to the river over the next few days. The weather forecast is dry Tuesday and Wednesday. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days, particularly on the River Glyme.  

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T11:59:57</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels have led to flooding of land close to the river.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue today, because river levels along the River Thames remain high, particularly in the Kempsford area. The weather forecast is dry Tuesday and Wednesday. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T13:04:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible today in the Bourton on the Water area. The weather forecast is dry Tuesday and Wednesday. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T12:00:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>Flood risk remains possible.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue as river levels remain high, especially in the Lechlade area. The weather forecast is dry Tuesday and Wednesday. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T12:00:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries on the Upper River Thames above Cricklade</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T10:38:05</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are falling but remain high, therefore the risk of flooding continues on 23 December and over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgeley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. Predicted peaks:- Mythe peaked at 4.13m on 21/12, Haw Bridge peaked at 4.97m 21/12. We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T08:02:16</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T16:24:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>High river levels have led to flooding of land close to the river.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue, as the River Thames remains high. The weather forecast is dry Tuesday and Wednesday. We do not expect the river to rise further, however river levels will remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T13:04:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T09:01:01</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T09:00:58</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T09:00:56</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Coln and its tributaries</title>
      <description>Flooding remains possible.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected, especially around Fossebridge and Bibury. The weather forecast is dry Tuesday and Wednesday. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days. We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 

Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00PM, midday, on the 24 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-23T12:00:19</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
