<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>Areas most at risk include low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected. Weather conditions have improved today but further rainfall is forecast from tomorrow Thursday 04/12/25. River levels are falling slightly but will remain high and are likely to rise again in response to the forecast rainfall later this week and into the weekend.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T12:44:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible today, 03 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, along the River Churn around Cerney Wick. The weather forecast is mostly dry today, with further rain expected on Thursday.  We expect river levels to remain high today.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 18:00 03 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:53:05</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible today, 03 Dec 2025.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, along the River Evenlode near Shipton-under-Wychwood. The weather forecast is mostly dry today, with further rain expected on Thursday.  We expect river levels to remain high today.

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 18:00 03 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:49:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. 

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today, 03 Dec 2025, along the River Thames, especially in the Kempsford area. This is as a result of rivers responding to recent rainfall. The weather forecast is mostly dry today, with further rain expected on Thursday.  We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 18:00 03 Dec 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:55:17</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:47:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are currently rising due to rainfall on Monday, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgeley. The Severn Ham, Tewkesbury may start to fill.  

Predicted peaks:-  
Mythe 3.1m to 3.7m 05/12/2025 PM. 
Haw Bridge 4.0m to 4.7m 05/12/2025 PM. 

Tides are increasing from Wednesday until the weekend. River levels at Sandhurst and Gloucester will be influenced by these tides. Current predictions: 

Sandhurst 2.9m to 3.1m 03/12/2025 PM and 3.0m to 3.2m 04/12/2025 AM.  
Gloucester 2.5m to 2.8m 03/12/2025 PM and 2.8m to 3.1m 04/12/2025 AM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.   
This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 4 December 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:29:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:15:06</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T14:14:54</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels are currently rising due to rainfall on Monday, subsequently flooding may continue over the next few days. 
Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains may affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St and Waterside Gates are closed at Upton upon Severn.   

Predicted peaks:- 
Bewdley 3.0m to 3.8 m 04/12/2025 PM. 
Worcester 3.4m to 4.1m 04/12/2025 OVERNIGHT. 
Diglis 3.0m to 3.7m 05/12/2025 AM. 
Kempsey Yacht Club 5.0m to 5.7m 05/12/25 AM. 
Saxons Lode 4.1m to 4.7m 05/12/25 PM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.  Consider the installation of property flood resilience measures 

This message will be updated by 09:00AM on 4 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-03T08:31:21</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
