<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>The flood risk remains.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue, river levels are high along the River Churn, near Cerney Wick. The weather forecast is for dry conditions to continue through today, 29 December, overnight and into tomorrow. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00, midday, on the 30 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T08:49:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Windrush from Bourton to Newbridge</title>
      <description>The flood risk remains.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is expected to continue as river levels along the River Windrush remain high, particularly in Bourton on the Water and Newbridge areas. The weather forecast is for dry conditions to continue through today, 29 December, overnight and into tomorrow. We expect river levels to remain high over the next few days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00, midday, on the 30 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T08:53:06</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T08:55:28</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>The flood risk remains.

Flooding of low lying land and roads remains possible in the Bourton on the Water area. The weather forecast is for dry conditions to continue through today, 29 December, overnight and into tomorrow. We expect river levels to remain high over the coming days.

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 12:00, midday, on the 30 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T08:52:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Leach from Northleach to Mill Lane near Lechlade</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T16:20:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Thames and tributaries from Buscot Wick down to Kings Lock</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T08:56:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Coln and its tributaries</title>
      <description>The flood risk remains.

Flooding of low lying land and road remains possible around Fossebridge. The weather forecast is for dry conditions to continue through today, 29 December, overnight and into tomorrow. River levels are slowly falling but are expected to remain high over the coming days. 

We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 12:00, midday, on the 30 December 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-12-29T08:50:18</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
