<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Ditch in between Salvation Army force &amp; House Of Halo and Co, 29th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8478594</link>
<description>House Of Halo and Co 41 Bath Rd, Cheltenham GL53 7HQ 01242 463629&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Hair by Mia Luby House Of Halo and Co, 41 Bath Rd, Cheltenham GL53 7HQ 07711 214316&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is why not to build Government services businesses along landlord an private business fences. Look in between the Ditch. How long it been like that? Would you realize the 2 hair shop not reporting the matter, tomorrow inspect what they came to work an do. Is it making they money? Who&amp;#39;s to build without reporting spreading the plant internal. Can cause the root growing through they building.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Look at the prove gave me shelter on 28th November 2025. The Salvation Army Community Church Cheltenham The Salvation Army Church, 39 Bath Rd, Cheltenham GL53 7HG. After the Police Officer treated me like that. On the 28th November 2025 around 2am I was sleeping at Waitrose &amp;amp; Partners Cheltenham Honeybourne Way, Cheltenham GL50 3QW an Indian pakistan guy came behind the CCTV waking me up showing an blue plastic told if wants an Beer showing as face expression. He notice Henry in the sleeping bag. If he don’t to give up on life. He go around who innocent test if something knows his mind if made pain release Trigger off mumbling. Look if the police stop searching. Why would he seeing me suffering offering 🍺 look if Lizzy came from Camberwell London hiding around following an people in the homeless centre hiding her from him. Look if they speaking to her. Henry suspect an shouting out give him back his things. Made him express his feelings look as Queen Elizabeth II resemblance when take off makeup old time days they find pig, look if picking up Cigarette butt&amp;#39;s, wearing Leggings she was before an hiding from Henry made other male following plus the Indian Pakistan guy she go in car with not telling Henry who is he? What is his full name from 2019 is she still speaking to him? Now she around White guys knows me an testing if she like them fake love for sex after her in houses. Suspect Edward Fleming shout white guys is an Rapist than Reading through Henry life story suspect marshall after her started to show me hate. Just because of this girl lexi Ferries ride on a motorbike. Had an accident Claiming compensation police officer allowed her gathering evidence using her family in hospital solicitors prove her family is Judge if work in the order pay her out. But not putting her in hospital Mental health suspect her intention smoking cannabis hate Henry wish rape keep on coming around to be in the house Edward keep on Threatened punch in the face told guys run in his house done something an he mention called a police. If this is people lying sake of the Police. Why not give him Justice? As her claiming accident motorbike work accident. They live at 34 Pennine Rd GL52 5HE Cheltenham lexi only told live in Gloucester go there to small cannabis 24/7 investigate peroner informing on drugs , dealer, using Bank transfer, drink Alcohol pretend as Drunk using Marshall rape her as prostitute. Using Edward is the owner with friends Chris, liam an Marshall all on benefit stealing Drugs using hearing voices ringing noise but hospital do not put them in the category. Name it tinnitus. Expose running an holding they ears go to the hospital is that an Coincident take so much sleeping pills. See if told referred you to specialist send it over to GP name it tinnitus sending them to groups all in the category.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Did none of these people report. Why living off Benefit Claim? And none single homeless suffering food poison. He spite Henry Edward using chemical spray, bleach. Giving tobacco, blow his nose, do not shower, please inspect check his body. How would he buy his house. Using Police bad influence, motivating him. Not to work gets better. How long? Why not tell off the police officer. He buy his house how would he maintain? Eat food? Spite all of his residents to Claim benefit an might pay him housing benefit are out of the universal credit payment. He hurt Henry keep on lying pick Marshall side. Might wants to pick trouble. Lizzy might have friends an they hate Henry an seeing if can bring them in they houses use paying cheap rent. Fixing up using christmas. See what Edward did kick Henry out heard her on the police bye. Blocked him with her family in employment use her family in Anchor House an Julian House put his name in debts showing government systems see the prove. Now the police officer using they order wants permission after mental health an free benefit Claim if use take medication an have entitled eligible as the purpose. Why cannot ship him back to his country. If told credit card finance, loan. How much money the police working an save in the bank. Would she pick Benefit Claim? No kids single homeless poor cannot read. For her boyfriend kids family are her self. Than why she picking it for Henry life?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I was at trinity Church King&amp;#39;s Table.work at Julian House Phil did me wrong. Gave me an safe house Anchor House rent over £450 threatened to put on Housing Benefit if do not applied for Universal Credit. They never give an agreement but wanted Henry take it to the Police Station an see if work in the order Actually using it put on universal credit, find Accommodation pay housing Benefit but do not wants to came back to his country. See when not appreciate. She throw it in His Majesty King Charles III face waste Queen Elizabeth II money if she pass away don&amp;#39;t say nothing still do the same. What is hiding? An African lady sit in the police station than an young African boy speaking to her as friends. She wearing Makeup an not seen her surrounding voice record through the window, spite Henry how she gets caught. He do not knows nothing what she hold behind. He should hear positive. Not sending emails phone an might holding things against him without tell nothing. All it is give him justice not to make things escalate. Spite Henry told the Emergency Service only comes out for life an death. So he told disrespecting him after mental health look at the African boy after him than her kids but she don&amp;#39;t care if pain an suffer is what human cannot take. Just her to owned up an show Henry hate. He spoke about Muslim an Indian pakistan she might wants to put him off, told did an somalian boy die? Behind Henry no police approach but went to his Step dad check out the dog. How did they knows? She spite Henry using the pass, he bring up someone throw a chair in his leg. Only pick out McDonald&amp;#39;s suing. He suffering in the cold he notice all she after mental health an free benefit if she his case hate him. Why not ship him back to his country. He told how long give up 2020 to 2025 she heard he is not intelligent have Common Sense do not rape not an Child Molester, Rapist. She heard take life sentence an he finish it off. Apologize live honest. What would she judge? Did she putting up on social media? After aggressive. Why not give the person justice? Did she do no investigation? Knows makeup is illegal do not wants him to pick out office scripts to explain as Rishi Sunak in the house of parliament have his wife secured. Can eat healthy, shower heater. What they after to judge? Is it calling problems for his brain? Are pick out impossible unbelievable out of books TV shows, using it without telling the person. What books an movie not allowed to read have owned opinions what witness she do not believe an after what is it? Holding behind? Henry might thought she do not wants to hear the Queen wants his head by an Police Officer in 2016 he told an police lady he coming down to the Station to give an statement she actually told when locking off. Is it the reason? Who knows. Would she have a report the day when henry walked not after are today explain. Why using mental health an free benefit when he told Fraud Scammed DWP PIP Mobility plus Housing Benefit did he not have his evidence case, reference. Why treated that way. She wants a question to put a cross, without have her statement report right dear and then without a question to answer owned up an tell the reason in record electric notes, bad report. Look if that is the statement mental health asked doctor medication are wants to test gets criminal damage hide in aggravated, swearing, inappropriate insulted an caught out frozen is brain in the cool. Cannot think focus. An still use if feeling pain if wants to see an doctor are you taking medication another than pain release if done already told. That is a life she destroy. Look if have family kids in Henry age group. Did she treat anyone like that? Bad influence not to motivate be a user failure, loser.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Not to fight his case he use an white skinny young girl out of the blue coming in open door to prove can gets attention. If don&amp;#39;t have no bottom. Playing mind game to check her out. If secret law affecting her in TV Channel pick Characters made up movie. A inspect moving in her body an she suspect it is secret law affecting her unexpected as how hide. She find Henry woman lizzy behind. She watching if not wearing makeup than suddenly this is when started going in open door wearing leggings. I suspect find the insect to blame swelling up her body parts. If notice the risk cannot report it to the police. She look in to Mental Health Questions an find threatened patient and she learn outsmart inspect take in. Use it not to tell the truth. Why she cannot report what she hide an done from an child plus having spite with the secret. Intentionally using it against Lizzy to witness the save result. Notice why they wearing makeup. See if told following fashion. Asked Questions. Predict mind is like an Channel. Watching people on YouTube Facebook actress celebrity musician. Find Princess and Prince around them. If wants to be better hide them in mind an use it features to hold the secret if living the best life an blame it in the Channel using Secret law to Affect them. If mind is unknown show them what they did. Before owned up. So Henry use Movie as Acton to create the book of life. All the wrongs human can hold in an live to pretend following rules. It is an risk when die. We do not knows if there is mind reader are life after death. Have faith if God knows our thoughts an movement we bring it out of the mind. If live by Principle the school that taught to understand the brain never use lie an pretend to live unworthy. Was an child once now as an adult the brain reminds. If this work out. Asked did any one hide an break the law from an child. Never see police just following company loads astray. Find excited in activity an all about sex in school boyfriend and girlfriend. Did you hide behind parents watching inappropriate videos Pornographic, adult movie? Did you notice kiss to make love is the access. Female giving the male to gets in the mode in deep feelings. No one around the child break work out sex can happened the male desperate if friends school kids find it excited teasing if not having. Did you made your mistake hear? An went off feel release parents came in. Live normal forgot the next day, this is when brother sister cousin can gets used to each other. Anywhere they go can try because no one around an just looking out if family adult people in public not to caught them. How far it can lead if your parents not strict.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Really not securing our country. This is the reason why evil bring out fault with the secret to give more intention have spite if cannot take pain an suffer. One example if made an movie disappear through wall in the building an came outside. See why take out impossible unbelievable out of TV Channel. Now use comparance PC an human Brain connect can function. Use it in an another situation for the combination inclusive sex food keep but needs money for the control if take out money do they Automatic keep the 2? Find ideas eyes 👀 as CCTV, ears 👂like voice record, speaker like voices mouth. Tone of the voice.Turn it down, speak in mind, Turn up the volume , speak out , put the t v mute. Find can planned plot make Preparation come out of writing no teacher no judge find the result is think in mind do not tell no one. Just keep it. If call the police, face the judge use your life destroy if tell the truth can go to jail gets expose on news Whole World use it as the whole school. Find assembly graduation now in public entertaining stadium champion winner have jobs gained qualification have conversation reading writing that is what you have confidence in. But to practice telling the truth not doing that to gets over it find shy embarrassed shameful not to gets expose. Be foolish hold secret as personal issue problems an destroy others life. If eating the animal meat. Live normal living under money use paying bills rent providing for mother and father with kids. Find purpose rent expensive finance mortgage do not wants to lose out on profit. Find it is slave nothing for nothing.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please inspect in the ditch heard mind the Gap. Just remember the Crowd an evil find death if think of all the ways not coming back alive rethink all the ways coming back alive. God forbid testing if something knows they mind hold as hostage can Chopped up body parts as distribute scrap metal, pick general waste than comes back in recycle. Heard Queen wants a person head think about robot push in member card hard drive. Find sex getting greedy food quality expensive things. How worst can it gets. Pain internal plus how cold it gets suffer what is the option? Suicide if you in doors in relationship living in comfortable. What about those that hide done so much wrongs an find God not real by work out the comparance come out of impossible unbelievable in TV Channel an notice the School Questions answer true or false. If eyes is the prove without an CCTV Footage is that no Evidence? If Police not giving no justice after them to do Crime using life or death. How spite you can gets. Secret law Affecting notice is it because of the wrongs Law Punish for attempted locked up Prisoner. Why after Mental health find Accommodation using eligible entitled? Without no jobs but growing up they kids family. Inspect watching them buy houses have kids risk working. Use putting your name in debts. If notice no police around Attempted go back again if use the Night dark find someone sitting behind a computer moving a mouse. What if technology explore shut internet electricity. Can they test hold as hostage use Gang violence if gets away with fighting hold weapons running boys down all fear use it for protection hold as guard strike for defence if attack heard Self Defence. Find can go Jail run off using Automatic Reaction Frightened scared panic fretting Alert Danger stop what you doing it is the Emergency Service. If something as an insect putting you down disable, pain cannot stand, can expose mumbling as an monkey known for Handicap. Now if Police Officers not giving no justice. What you they intention be? Using spite if they have permission how it feel. Watching them hide for sex an wants them suffer which mistakes bigger? Child Molester Rapist are hide with sister brother cousin from young an run out to Stranger holding the secret an now working for the police.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;That is how treating them. To wish affect back they family kids with the secret plus the Police Officer if they mistakes cannot comes back made them perfect as she be around the Majesty work for the law. Not to be Punish in the cold locked up in jail. No sex, food, vehicles houses expensive things. Have spite if she hide for sex not giving no justice an enjoying what destroy they life from an child Temptation hiding behind parents close an wants them have spite Murderer steal still affect them with the secret. Pick jail are Mental health no jobs only putting they names in debts. What about credit card finance loans if not working can steal don&amp;#39;t show the system an pay back through tax as employment. Why not find solution. Use Rishi Sunak how much tax he paid an pay the same amount tax in Henry name. Let&amp;#39;s put in to the tax are give Rishi Sunak all the benefits claimed in Henry name Child Disability Allowance cannot made him grow up poor cannot read an they teasing calling names Dumb indian Pakistan report he have learning difficulties to the school GP Southwark Council God forbid than when pass 1 year over 19 set him up with 3 cousin in his family use Government workers move him right next to the house. Use he not having sex no relationship he cannot be gay. If witness at the party club stadium a Crime involved run off might knows who done it. Still not report to the police. Henry suspect hold Lizzy for this witness are she done something for the law but she an Prince Harry they wanted an little baby are take Virginity Pregnancy an she be shy embarrassed hold the secret for permanent. Now they following her around if she fake love an they wants sex. Test watching wish rape messed up Queen Elizabeth II tradition. If she live Henry take find he is nothing in permission test coming close an Lizzy hiding not telling Henry nothing who she speaking with what is they names as friends after to fake love for sex. See why wants Henry feel pain internal test the solution. Put Rishi Sunak names in debts Claim DWP PIP Mobility plus Housing Benefit. Have him with no family no kids if go in hospital Jail, no one can discharge him, Help him give jobs in they private business apply for jobs reject his application only agency. Street, cleaning or delivery, have him homeless live in public. No justice? Henry made him fight his case all from the pass can bring back as updated. So if Henry told feeling pain is it because not working? Are putting his name in debts? Is it because using NHS no hospital fees police allowed Doctors and nurses not giving patient, a full receipt, all the names. What happened when discharged. They threatened playing paranoid taking bloods days weeks months if comes back again do the same. This is what they hide in. Just because an police officer cannot take pain suffer. Find test aggressive show her the secret by telling her feeling pain made it serious knows the secret in the system. She find threatened asked Questions Doctors and medication. Why not ship him backed to his country. If cannot made him face His Majesty King Charles III are Prime Minister Keir Starmer. She wants them attempted Damage someone an see what happened. Find Henry to use if after sex an baby hold in jail are Hospital an they family witness pain suffer paralyse, cripple. By Henry prove to the Police he is feeling pain that is how she can suspect it is the system an hold him down made they family be around feed give medication put in supported find accommodation put on all the benefits an wait as Rishi Sunak getting old hide in gain weight not exercising, eating take medication. Look at that. Why not give the person work compensation pay back all the benefits Claim in his name as Rishi Sunak are ship him backed to his country. They do not wants to put in the system. Fraud Scammed Child disability allowance, Fraud PIP Mobility plus Housing Benefit now ship him Back to his country without his work Compensation on the claim accident injury. See if try this solution? Are made the Police Officer write her full life story. Pass on to Her Majesty Queen Camilla plus Princess Kate an Meghan. If witness the secret in the law. Come across what Henry experience are she pick TV Channel disappear. Test bump your head in the wall jump Out from the window. How is that possible is that mad dumb. Only if they gets permission use it. So Henry call for His Majesty King Charles III an Prince William an Harry. If made any one in public kill murderer attempted to rape. Without write your full life story an see if never experience what Henry witness. Clear all the dangers in the community. Stop roadworker, street sweeper an give gardening jobs. Cut down all the big trees put out of public safety, remove all the wild trees spreading along the fences.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Stop putting Queen Elizabeth II an King Philip family in danger plus King Charles III an Queen Camille. Prince William an Harry Princess Kate an Meghan family kids in danger.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Why not give slave if have free School, Free Hospital, free college, free university, free library, free army, free police force, free fire brigade, free jobs, free private businesses just do anything for money go on YouTube, trading lottery bitcoin. Why not give work for free to prisoner, unemployed, who playing Mental health take medication an just sit at home. Can they walk? Use they hands? Follow instruction demonstration give induction. Training Health and safety. Manual lifting. Now if who in public wants to commit Crime no one blame suffering in the cold Starve no savings no profit because government an Majesty family take over all the jobs an no Confession destroy they tooth rotting not showing, diseases, sleeping in bushes tents, shops, supermarket library, in building parks, breaking garage premises... Why Destroying the Majesty kindness give Government the permission. Don&amp;#39;t care about the environment living? Now test if Henry live with his problems until die. What about who in public doing Crime stealing Drugs Leader, test if comes for slave are continue working rich become billionaire working hard for what they have.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Make sure Write your full life story no more celebration. Having sex before work after work write on the weekend write soon as finish call the Emergency Service an felt sorry. Pick out the biggest things, anything gets an chance go court have it to show the judge, gather all your family do the same. What Henry got to do? If Police cannot find solution compare Rishi Sunak grown up Henry balance, take out of decrease. An put in increase balance. Both ways hot and cold temperature for the whether climate he find what happened to his parents family on benefit should happened to Queen Elizabeth II and King Philip family if made Confession as poor not them in permission only poor he find to victimize. Using the secret in the law he experience.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Now Henry live positive you have the Choice. Help are live as don&amp;#39;t care not living under rules living under money. All human do not wants to work as you. Use benefit Claim but not your kids. Do you care anyway? If pain an suffer if what all human cannot take plus single poor lonely Sadness&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Remember at Edward Fleming address there is an primary school. Inspect his garden spreading plants 🪴 he mention something regarding the school kids, he using the wild plants growing on the fence to block them out as a blind curtain. This is getting serious. Henry report to the school an he kick him out for lexi. Inspect the house what happening if on benefit found out the prove&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8478594.0.jpeg?2164d25b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bath Road, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8478594&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8478594</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897396 -2.073748</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road sign damaged and missing, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8478199</link>
<description>Moorend park grove&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Moorend Grove, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8478199&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street nameplates</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8478199</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.879305 -2.081945</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hubcap on outside lane just before roundabout, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477786</link>
<description>THere was a hubcap in the middle of the outside lane approaching the Junction 11A roundabout from the northbound exit as of Friday c.4.45pm. Cars were swerving to avoid it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brockworth Interchange, Brockworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477786&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Road surface (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477786</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.857623 -2.168098</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Whole road of aprox 400 metres, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477753</link>
<description>The road surface is covered in pot holes and in a generally very bad condition.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477753&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477753</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892517 -2.005185</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There is a large traffic cone and frame for a road sign left, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477744</link>
<description>The traffic cone is by the lights on the side of verge and the frame for a road sign is slightly further along by the entrance to the park.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 31, Wymans Lane, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477744&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477744</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.920316 -2.091671</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Failure to do stated works as stated in your letter Ref 11495612 dated 10 Nov 25, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477675</link>
<description>Gloucester St, Winchcombe. Intended yellow line painting work has required no parking on road between 24-28 Nov 25. No work was actually done by you. Where would you like me to send my car park fees to for the period that you stopped me parking outside my house but didn&amp;#39;t actually do the work you stated in the reference you were due to do? You have left restricted parking cones in place; why? You had your stated restricted parking period to do the work but you failed to execute it so I assume the cones are no longer valid.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 83, Gloucester Street, Winchcombe, Winchcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477675&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Line issue (Parking)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477675</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.952016 -1.970829</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unpermitted roadworks problem, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477674</link>
<description>TM not required as there are no works going on. Also these are for works off of the carriageway. Why couldn&amp;#39;t these have been removed over the weekend. &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477674&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Unpermitted roadworks</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477674</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.942534 -2.021007</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Arm chair dumped and small mound of earth, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477583</link>
<description>Someone has flytipped a armchair and left a mound of earth&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8477583.0.jpeg?d4452d0a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 67, Clyde Crescent, Lynworth, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477583&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477583</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.906552 -2.052738</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cable run under pavement and over verge, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477570</link>
<description>Cable run form 39 Merriville Road under pavement over verge and into caravan&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 16, Merriville Road, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477570&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477570</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907625 -2.102463</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole in Beeches Road, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477490</link>
<description>Pothole in the middle of the road opposite number 21. On a bus route so it wears quickly.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 23, Beeches Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477490&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477490</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 15:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.877824 -2.047772</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Three Lights out on Roundabout, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477480</link>
<description>The three lights are all out on the column in the middle of the roundabout at the junction of Hales Road and Hewlett Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): B4075, Battledown, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477480&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477480</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 15:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900792 -2.054511</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole at entrance to Robinia Close, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477376</link>
<description>Growing pothole just at the turn from Maple Drive to Robinia Close.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 32, Maple Drive, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477376&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477376</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.8787 -2.045119</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477237</link>
<description>Series of potholes as you join roundabout. Note also many area with failed drainage edges&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road, Elmbridge, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477237&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477237</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878649 -2.201094</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple large potholes. Road surface falling apart., 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477180</link>
<description>Opposite the allotments on Old Gloucester Road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8477180.0.jpeg?921d04e2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 29, Hayden Road, Hesters Way, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477180&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477180</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.916974 -2.118514</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The drain is blocked problem, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477138</link>
<description>Broken missing section of gully&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477138&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477138</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.871633 -2.052987</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerb stone an surrounding tarmac surface damaged, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477084</link>
<description>Outside 55 Gretton Road. This has been cause by 2 weeks of traffic (606 Bus, farm vehicles, lorries) mounting the kerb due to the 3 way traffic light system that has been in place for the last to weeks for the new sewer works to service the new development opposite Privet Court&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please note that the tarmac finish of the pavement along a long of kerb/drop kerb stones has also fatigued and shows minor cracking that over the winter months and frost expand and deteriorate and will need to have a new skim finish applied.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Can this repair be scheduled at the earliest opportunity?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8477084.0.jpeg?bc2534f5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 30,32, Gretton Road, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477084&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The kerb is damaged/missing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8477084</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.965051 -2.046847</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Water company have complained that they cannot access their cover because of excess pavement material that is from when it was resurfaced, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476467</link>
<description>The drain is located within the Spectre&amp;#39;s seating area outside the pub on the High Street&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8476467.0.jpeg?46f1a23c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 73-75, High Street, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476467&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476467</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 12:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898377 -2.071645</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dumped Car, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476360</link>
<description>Probably been used in a crime considering where it’s been dumped&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8476360.0.jpeg?83c0cebc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 29, Gristmill Close, Springbank, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476360&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476360</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 12:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.914588 -2.121331</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bus stop, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476333</link>
<description>Serious design error on the placement of the bus stop at Pirton Corner (Churchdown) another part of the (Game Changer) cycle spine .As the bus approach’s Pirton stop from Hare and Hounds the driver has to have Second Sight it s impossible to see waiting Customers (alas no shelter ) and to indicate to the On coming driver you have to stand on the traffic light island ,this needs to be sorted .&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pirton Lane, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476333&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Bus stop/shelter issue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476333</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.885053 -2.190359</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Shurdingto Road path barriers down, 28th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476306</link>
<description>User are mis guided onto un tarmac path construction&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8476306.0.jpeg?78f11311&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shurdington Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476306&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign bracket is hanging/fallen off (Non illuminating sign)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8476306</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.88115 -2.093623</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>