<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Small pile of asbestos roofing, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739499</link>
<description>A pile of roofing, which appears to be corrugated asbestos has been left on the side of the road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Oxenton, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739499&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739499</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.972563 -2.077109</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep pothole at the top of Badgeworth bridge, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739480</link>
<description>There is a really deep pothole towards the left side of the road as we reach the top of the bridge driving from Badgeworth towards Reddings. As the road narrows at this point, drivers trying to avoid the pothole are having to veer right straight onto oncoming traffic, and both sides have no visibility of each other at this point. This could result in a serious accident anytime. I had a near miss today. I’m aware that this bridge has had multiple fixes in recent years. However we’ve now seen a number of potholes appearing again up and down the bridge slopes. Please could you inspect and fix these urgently as this is a main thoroughfare and a bus route.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badgeworth Road, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739480&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739480</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884252 -2.142579</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep pothole on Grovefield way at pedestrian crossing, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739466</link>
<description>There is a deep pothole at the pedestrian crossing on Grovefield way on the left carriageway while driving from Arle court towards Symphony road. This is situated just before turning left into Symphony road. The position of the pothole is towards the right side of the crossing and it caused damage to my car’s front right tyre and wheel rim. I request you to kindly check and fill this pothole at the earliest.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Grovefield Way, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739466&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739466</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884916 -2.131429</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Huge gigantic big crater, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739449</link>
<description>Big crack in the road, pretty soon we will need a bridge to get over it. Almost broke the front end of my partners car&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Andover Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739449&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739449</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893105 -2.089916</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Series of potholes on Badgeworth bridge, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739445</link>
<description>There are a series of potholes at the bottom of the slope of the Badgeworth bridge on the left carriageway while travelling from Badgeworth towards the Reddings. The camber on the road and oncoming traffic forces vehicles to drive straight into these potholes, resulting in damages to the front left tyres. Please could you inspect these and fix the road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badgeworth Road, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739445&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739445</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 23:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886137 -2.142778</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flooding highway culvert on footpath, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739279</link>
<description>Mh cover located at front of Roseville is flooding out and overflowing in heavy rain. Severn Trent have attended and this is not their issue&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2, Shurdington Road, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739279&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739279</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.868306 -2.111126</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Impossible to avoid huge pothole in carriagway on bridge, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739146</link>
<description>On apex of humpback railway bridge in the left hand carriageway as you head from badgeworth towards arle court roundabout. Pothole is so large now that it cannot be avoided. Already causing vehicle damage despite several reports on this platform. It is now going to cause a road accident due to location of pothole, as drivers are moving into the oncoming carriageway on a blind apex to avoid it, or being thrown into the oncoming carriageway after hitting it when driving in the dark. GET IT FIXED! Dont rely on having photographs as this is a very dangerous section of the road to expect anyone to stop and take photographs at, just fix it as its been getting worse for months!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badgeworth Road, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739146&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739146</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884295 -2.142468</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Length of cycle path down B4063 very muddy, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739038</link>
<description>This applies to a lot of the cycle path, but especially near gates on the field. For months now the path has been getting in increasingly poor condition, really needs sweeping as it&amp;#39;s getting increasingly hazardous to cycle down.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gloucester Road, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739038&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739038</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900185 -2.15796</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large depp pothole, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739016</link>
<description>On the left heading away from the village towards A435 just by the pedestrian safety island&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Finlay Way, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739016&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8739016</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.948923 -2.065555</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large pothole and damage on Lansdown Road, near jct with Lansdown Parade, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738944</link>
<description>Really large and deep pothole where Lansdown Road continues past Texaco petrol station towards Montpellier roundabout. The pothole is right as the traffic diverges, just after the junction with Lansdown parade.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Really wide and square pothole, which could cause serious damage at speed. In the dark it’s really hard to see and requires swerving to avoid. Has been like this for weeks.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lansdown Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738944&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738944</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893589 -2.089883</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole and failing repairs, Hewlett Road beside school, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738926</link>
<description>Potholes and road damage at the end of the row of parked cars along Hewlett Road, right by Berkhampstead School.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Damage includes cracks, deep and wide pothole, and uneven road surface.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 169, Hewlett Road, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738926&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738926</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901525 -2.05975</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Water flowing out of cottage verge causing significant water to flow onto road causing dangerous conditions., 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738892</link>
<description>Bottom of cottage garden.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Large amount of water flowing for over a year. This will be extremely dangerous if it freezes.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8738892.0.jpeg?0c308f06&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bushcombe Lane, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738892&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738892</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.946594 -2.042048</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large pothole in Bethesda St., 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738829</link>
<description>Large and deep pothole. Cars parked on one side of the road means it can’t be avoided when exiting Bath Rd car park&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Upper Bath Street, Tivoli, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738829&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738829</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.890326 -2.080671</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Floodwater at pedestrian crossing, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738803</link>
<description>Standing water sitting at pedestrian crossing- blocking access to the crossing button. The footpath is flooded and so pedestrians are forced to use the cycle path or grass next to the crossing. Unsafe. Close proximity to a school on a very busy junction. Unacceptable thst this has not been speedily rectified!&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8738803.0.jpeg?c4fd9b35&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Central Cross Drive, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738803&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>No rain in 24 hours - water has increased or remained the same</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738803</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907738 -2.06997</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flooding/ Poor road surface, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738598</link>
<description>Between Gotherington railway bridge and turn off to Dixton.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Even though there has been rain in the last 24 hours, when there hasn’t been this section of road takes ages to drain as there seems to be no drainage. It is a major hazard as cars drive in the middle of the road where theres some surface still visible to avoid the dangerous surface below the water. It really needs looking into asap as there’s going to be an accident sooner or later. The whole Gretton/ Gotherington Road needs resurfacing as there’s multiple issues.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gretton Road, Prescott, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738598&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>No rain in 24 hours - water has increased or remained the same</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738598</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.968387 -2.030629</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in road problem, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738525</link>
<description>pothole - bad pothole - he was walking no damdge there are two - these are inbetween parked cars &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738525&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738525</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901384 -2.06062</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple pothole on Mill Lane and Vicarage lane junction, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738288</link>
<description>These potholes were filled before Christmas but have now returned worse than they were before.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Mill Lane, Brockworth, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738288&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738288</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.848768 -2.156426</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Huge pothole over the railway bridge, which caused my tire to punchure, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738286</link>
<description>Huge pothole over the railway bridge, heading towards Kingsditch lane. My tire punctured as a result&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8738286.0.jpeg?fd6464b0&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Thompson&#39;s Way, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738286&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738286</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.915394 -2.09279</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Many deep potholes getter worse, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738168</link>
<description>Outside no 25&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8738168.0.jpeg?465b9fca&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 21, Hearne Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738168&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738168</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.883693 -2.047276</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potholes and broken road surface, 21st January</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738138</link>
<description>About 100m down the hill from the air balloon roundabout the road is breaking up badly. It’s on the coloured surface.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It’s getting rough with bigger holes forming&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A417, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738138&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8738138</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.841514 -2.102833</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>